Woodward, S.C. mss. 1767-1961 LMC 2207
Lilly Library
Woodward, S.C. mss.
1767-1961
Lilly Library
Woodward, S.C.
LMC 2207
1 folio oversize
6 Boxes 6 standard
The Woodward, S.C. mss., 1767-1961, consist of correspondence, autographs and pictures of actors, actresses, managers, dramatists, musicians, and other persons connected with the theatre from the collection of Sidney C. Woodward, journalist.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Biographical Note
S.C. Woodward was a journalist, art critic for the Christian Science Monitor, and director of the Casson Galleries.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: I. Correspondence, II. Bound materials, III. Printed, IV. Photgraphs, and V. Folders. Materials are arranged chronologically in Correspondence and then alphabetically for the rest of the series.
Scope and Content Note
The persons represented are principally from England and the United States. The correspondence relates in the main to theatrical and personal matters. The pictures in the collection consist of photographs, engravings, and pictures clipped from periodicals and newspapers. Also included are two volumes of commonplace books by Mary Frances Scott-Siddons.
Acquisition Information
Acquired: 1973-1974.
Autographs --Collections.; Autographs --Collectors and collecting.; Autographs --Correspondence.; Journalists --Correspondence.; Theater --Great Britain.; Theater --United States.; Theater --History --18th century.; Theater --History --19th century.; Theater --History --20th century.; Motion picture film; Theater; Woodward, S.C.; Woodward, S. C.--Correspondence.; Burnett, Carol --Photographs.; Mansfield, Jayne, 1933-1967 --Photographs.; Newmar, Julie, 1933 ---Photographs.; Pickford, Mary, 1892-1979 --Photographs.; Power, Tyrone, 1797-1841 --Photographs.; Power, Tyrone, 1914-1958--Photographs.; Theatre Royal, Drury Lane (London, England)
- I. Correspondence. (Box 1)
  - 1767-1809 (Box 1)
  - 1810-1819 (Box 1)
  - 1820-1829 (Box 1)
  - 1830-1839 (Box 1)
  - 1840-1849 (Box 1)
  - 1850-1859 (Box 1)
  - 1860-1869 (Box 1)
  - 1870-1879 (Box 1)
  - 1880-1889 (Box 1)
  - 1890-1894 (Box 1)
  - 1895-1899 (Box 1)
  - 1900-1904 (Box 1)
  - 1905-1909 (Box 1)
  - 1910-1912 (Box 1)
  - 1913-1914 (Box 1)
  - 1915-1919 (Box 1)
  - 1920-1922 (Box 1)
  - 1923-1924 (Box 1)
  - 1925-1962 (Box 1)
  - A-B., indated (Box 1)
  - C-D., indated (Box 1)
  - E-G., indated (Box 1)
  - H-K., indated (Box 1)
  - L-M., indated (Box 1)
  - N-R., indated (Box 2)
  - S-Z., indated (Box 2)
- II. Bound Materials. (Box 2)
  - Commonplace books by Mary Frances Scott-Siddons, (2 volumes) (Box 2)
- III. Printed. (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, (2 folders) (Box 2)
- IV. Photographs. (Box 2)
  - Abba, Marta - Coward, Noel Pierce (Box 2)
    General
    Abba, Marta
    Abbott, _____
    Abington, Mrs. Frances (Barton), (Mrs. James Abington)
    Adam, Noelle
    Adams, Maude
    Addison, Laura
    Addor, Ady
    Aickin, James
    Ainley, Henry
    Albanese, Licia
    Alberghetti, Anna Maria
    Alboni, Marietta
    Alcock, Merle
    Alexander, Sir George
    Allen, Viola
    Alonso, Alicia
    Amara, Lucine
    Amparan, Belen
    Amru-Sani
    Anderson, Judith
    Anderson, Marie Antoinette
    Anderson, Owen
    Andree, Dorothy
    Andrews, Julie
    Anglin, Margaret
    Anthony, Grace
    Arbor, Ann
    Archer, Belle
    Ardeck, Agnes
    Arden, Eve
    Arliss, George
    Arnaud, G. Yvonne
    Arova, Sonia
    Arthur, Julia
    Asche, Oscar
    Ashcroft, Dame Peggy
    Astor, Mary
    Atkins, _____
    Atwood, Donna
    Aylwin, Jean
    Azalea
    Bacall, Lauren
    Bacon, Frank
    Baddeley, Hermoine
    Bailey, Pearl Mae
    Bainter, Fay Okell
    Baker, Carroll
    Ball, Lucille
    Bampton, Rose E.
    Bancroft, Anne
    Bancroft, Sir Squire Bancroft
    Bannerman, Margaret
    Bannister, John
    Bara, Theda
    Baranova, Irina
    Barrett, George
    Barrett, Lawrence Patrick
    Barrington, Rutland
    Barrow, Mrs. Julia (Bennett)
    Barry, Mrs. Ann (Street), (Mrs. Dancer) (Mrs. Crawford) (Mrs. Spranger Barry)
    Barry, Helen
    Barrymore, Ethel
    Barrymore, Lionel
    Bartley, Mrs. Sarah (Smith) (Mrs. George Bartley)
    Bass, Charles
    Bateman, Kate Josephine
    Bates, Blanche
    Bauer, Ina
    Bawn, Dorianne
    Baxley, Barbara
    Baxter, Anne
    Baylis, Meredeth
    Beaumont, Bertee
    Beaumont, Muriel
    Bellew, Harold Kyrle Money
    Bellew, Kyrle
    Bellin, Olga
    Belmont, Mrs. Eleanor Elsie (Robson) (Mrs. August Belmont)
    Ben Greet Players
    Bennett, Constance
    Bennett, George John
    Bennett, James
    Bennett, Wilda
    Bensley, Robert
    Bergen, Polly
    Bergh, Henry
    Bergner, Elisabeth
    Beriosova, Svetlana
    Bertrand, M.J.
    Besant, Mrs. Annie (Wood) (Mrs. Frank Besant)
    Best, Edna
    Bettis, Valerie
    Betty, William Henry West
    Bigley, Isabel
    Binney, Constance
    Blaine, Vivian
    Blair, Eugenie
    Blanchard, _____
    Blanche, Marie
    Bland, Mrs. Maria Teresa (Romanzini) (Mrs. George Bland)
    Blasi, Silvania
    Bloom, Claire
    Bollinger, Anne
    Bond, Jessie
    Bonheur, Rosa
    Booth, Edwin Thomas
    Booth, Shirley
    Bordoni, Irene
    Bori, Lucrezia
    Borkh, Inge
    Boucicault, Mrs. Agnes Kelly (Robertson) (Mrs. Dion Boucicault)
    Boucicault, Dion
    Bourchier, Arthur
    Bourskaya, Ina
    Bowers, Mrs. Elizabeth (Crocker) (Mrs. David P. Bowers)
    Boyar, Monica
    Brady, Alice
    Brainard, Margaret
    Braithwaite, Dame Lilian
    Brandon-Thomas, Amy Marguerite
    Brandt, _____
    Braslau, Sophie
    Brayton, Lily
    Brett, Stanley
    Brice, Fannie
    Britton, Hutin
    Brockwell, Gladys
    Brough, Mary
    Brougham, John
    Brown, _____
    Brown, Louise
    Bruce, Carol
    Buchanan, McKean
    Buckstone, John Baldwin
    Bulkley, _____
    Bull, Ole Bornemann
    Bunn, Alfred
    Burke, Billie
    Burnett, Carol
    Burroughs, Marie
    Burt, Laura
    Burton, William Evans
    Busby, Amy
    Busoni, Ferruccio Benvenuto
    Butterworth, Clara
    Cadell, Jean
    Cahier, Mrs. Sarah Jane (Mme. Charles Cahier)
    Callas, Marie Meneghini
    Calvert, Charles Alexander
    Calvert, Louis
    Caminita, Jacqueline
    Campanini, Cleofonte
    Campanini, Italo
    Campbell, Bartley
    Campbell, Mrs. Beatrice Stella (Mrs. Patrick Campbell)
    Caprice, June
    Carey, Joyce
    Carlisle, Alexandra
    Carlisle, Kitty
    Carpenter, Constance
    Carroll, Diahann
    Carroll, Lee
    Carson, Frances
    Carter, Janis
    Carter, Mrs. Leslie
    Caruso, Enrico
    Cary, Annie Louise
    Castagna, Bruna
    Castle, Mrs. Irene (Mrs. Vernon Blythe Castle)
    Castle Square Stock Company
    Caulfield, John
    Cavendish, Ada
    Caverly, Carol
    Cayvan, Georgia
    Celeste, Madame
    Chandler, Evelyn
    Channing, Carol
    Chaplin, Charles Spencer
    Chapman, _____
    Charisse, Cyd
    Charles, Pamela
    Chatterton, Ruth
    Cheatham, Kitty
    Cheri, Rose
    Christians, Mady
    Church, Sandra
    Churchill, Marguerite
    Churchill, Sarah
    Claire, Ina
    Clark, Marguerite
    Clarkson, Joan
    Cleveland, Grover
    Clive, Edward E.
    Coghlan, Rose
    Colbert, Claudette
    Coleman, Nancy
    Collins, Winnie
    Colman, George (2 folders)
    Compton, Fay
    Compton, Henry
    Conklin, Peggy
    Conner, Nadine
    Constantino, Florencio
    Conway, Shirl
    Cook, Augustus
    Cook, Barbara
    Cooke, George Frederick
    Cooper, _____
    Cooper, Gladys
    Cooper, John
    Cooper, Margaret
    Cooper, Miriam
    Corbett, James John
    Cornalba, Elena
    Cornell, Katharine
    Costa, Mary
    Cotrely, Emma
    Cottrelly, Mathilde
    Couldock, Charles Walter
    Courtneidge, Cicely
    Covent-Garden theatre
    Coward, Noel Pierce
  - Cowl, Jane-Holland, Edmund Milton (Box 3)
    Cowl, Jane
    Cowie, Laura
    Craft, Marcella
    Craig, Helen
    Crane, William Henry
    Crespigny, _____
    Creswick, William
    Cummings, Constance
    Cummings, Minnie
    Curtis-Verna, Maria
    Cushman, Charlotte Saunders
    Cutler, Kate
    Dalis, Irene
    D'Alroy, Evelyn
    Daly, Augustin
    D'Angelo, Gianna
    Dare, Phyllis
    D'sArmont, Marie Anne (Charlotte Corday)
    Darnell, Linda
    Darvas, Lili
    Davenport, Edward Loomis
    Davenport, Mrs. Fanny (Vining) (Mrs. Edward Loomis Davenport)
    Davidge, William Pleater
    Davies, Lilian
    Davies, Marion
    Davis, Fay
    Davis, Jessie Bartlett
    Davison, Mrs. Maria Rebecca
    Davy, Gloria
    Day, Edieth
    Day, Laraine
    De Banzie, Brenda
    Dean, Julia
    De Havilland, Olivia Mary
    Della Casa, Lisa
    De los Angeles, Victoria
    De Luca, Guiseppi
    De Mille, Cecil Blount
    De Reszke, Jean
    Deslys, Gaby
    Desmond, Irene
    Destinn, Emmy
    Devlin, James S.
    Dibdin, Charles
    Dickons, Maria
    Dickson, Dorothy
    Dickson, Muriel
    Dietrich, Marlene
    Dillon, Frances
    Dimond, William
    Dimond, William Wyatt
    Dixey, Henry E.
    Dixon, Caroline
    Dobbs, Mattiwilda
    Dodd, James William
    Dove, Billie
    Dowton, William
    Drake, Debbie
    Draper, Ruth
    Dreux, Lorraine
    Drew, John, 1827-1862
    Drew, John, 1853-1927
    Drew, Mrs. Louisa (Lane) (Mrs. John Drew)
    Drury Lane Theater
    Dubois, Camille
    Dunham, Katherine
    Dvorak, Ann
    Dyott, John
    Eadie, Dennis
    Eagels, Jeanne
    Eames, Clare
    Eames, Emma
    Eddy, Edward
    Edeson, Robert
    Ediss, Connie
    Edwards, Mardette
    Egerton, Lillian
    Eggerth, Marta
    Ehrhardt, Bess
    Ekberg, Anita
    Elg, Taina
    Elias, Rosalind
    Elliston, Daisy
    Elliston, Robert William
    Emery, John
    Emery, Winifred
    Essex, Catherine (Stephens), countess of
    Evans, Alice
    Evans, Madge
    Evans, Maurice
    Evelyn, Clara
    Evelyn, Judith
    Eyre, Sophie
    Faber, Leslie
    Fabray, Nanette
    Fairbanks, Douglas
    Fairbanks, Lucile
    Falton, Maude
    Farmer, Frances
    Farrar, Geraldine
    Farrell, Eileen
    Farrell, Glenda
    Farren, _____
    Farren, William 1754-1795
    Farren, William, 1786-1861
    Farren, William, 1825-1908
    Farrington, Nina
    Faversham, William Alfred
    Fawcett, George
    Fawcett, John
    Fechter, Charles Albert
    Fenn, Jean
    Fenwick, Irene
    Ferguson, Elsie
    Ferrer, Jose Vincente
    Field, Mary Katherine Keemle
    Fields, Gracie
    Fisk, James, Jr.
    Fiske, Minnie Maddern
    Fitzgerald, Cissie
    Fitziu, Anna
    Fitzwilliam, Frances [Fanny] Elizabeth
    Flagsted, Kristen
    Fleming, Ethel
    Fleming, William Maybury
    Florence, Katherine
    Floyd, Marie
    Fonda, Henry
    Fong, Amy
    Fontanne, Lynn
    Fonteyn, Dame Margot
    Foote, Samuel
    Forbes, Brenda
    Forbes-Robertson, Lady Gertrude (Elliott), (Lady Johnston Forbes-Robertson)
    Forbes-Robertson, Sir Johnston
    Ford, Ruth
    Forrest, Edwin
    Forrest, Sally
    Foster, Phoebe
    Fox, Della May
    Fracci, Carla
    Francine
    Francis, Arlene
    Franklin, Irene
    Frederick, Pauline
    Frew, Charles
    Frigenza, Trixie
    Froman, Jane
    Fujima, Masaya
    Fury, Blaze
    Gae, Nadine
    Gall, Yvonne Irma
    Galli-Curci, Amaelita
    Garcia, Manuel del Poplo Vicente
    Garde, Betty
    Garden, Mary
    Garrick, David
    Garrick, Mrs. David
    Garrison, Mabel
    Garson, Greer
    Gateson, Marjorie
    Gay, John
    Gaynor, Janet
    Gear, Luella
    Genn, Leo
    George, Grace
    George, Marie
    George, Yvonne
    Ghemer, L.
    Ghostley, Alice
    Gielgud, Sir Arthur John
    Gilbert, Allie
    Gilbert, John
    Gilbert, John Cecil
    Gillette, William Hooker
    Gilmore, Patrick Sarafield
    Gish, Lillian
    Gladmond, Joyce
    Glaser, Lulu
    Gluck, Alma
    Glyn, Isabella Dallas
    Glynn, Gertrude
    Gombell, Minnav
    Goodrich, William Marcellus
    Goodwin, Lesley
    Goodwin, Nathaniel Carl, Jr.
    Gordon, Kitty
    Gordon, Marjorie
    Gordon, Ruth
    Grace Kelly, consort of Rainier III
    Graham, Martha
    Gramatica, Emma
    Granger, Maude
    Grans, Louise
    Gray, Dolores
    Gray, Gilda
    Greenwood, Joan
    Greer, Frances
    Greet, Clare
    Gregg, Katherine
    Grey, Beryl
    Grey, Katherine
    Griffith, David Wark
    Grimaldi, Joseph
    Grossmith, George, Jr.
    Gueden, Hilde
    Guilbert, Yvette
    Guinness, Alec
    Gusieva, Nina
    Guy, Gladys
    Gwenn, Edmund
    Hackett, James Henry
    Hagen, Uta
    Haines, William Wister
    Hajos, Mitzi
    Hall, Henry
    Hamblin, Thomas Sowerly
    Hampden, Walter
    Hampton, Hope
    The Happy Ending
    Hardwicke, Sir Cedric Webster
    Harland, Julia
    Harley, John Pritt
    Harlowe, Sarah
    Harned, Virginia
    Harris, Julie
    Harrison, Alice
    Harrison, Rex Carey
    Harrison, Susan
    Harshaw, Margaret
    Hart, Audrey
    Hart. Dolores
    Hart, Moss
    Hart, William Surrey
    Harvey, Hattie
    Hasso, Signe
    Hay, Mary
    Hayden, Melissa
    Haye, Helen
    Hayes, Helen
    Hayes, Peter Lind
    Haynes, Minna (Gale)
    Heard, _____
    Heath, Caroline
    Held, Anna
    Hempel, Frieda
    Henderson, John
    Hepburn, Audrey
    Hepburn, Katharine
    Herman, Reinhild Ludwig
    Hill, W.J.
    Hiller, Wendy
    Hillard, Robert C.
    Hines, Elizabeth
    Hines, Jerome
    Hodges, Joy
    Holland, Edmund Milton
  - Holland, Joseph Jefferson-Nordica, Lillian (Box 4)
    Holland, Joseph Jefferson
    Holliday, Judy
    Holm, Celeste
    Holman, Joseph George
    Holman, Libby
    Holmes, Terry
    Hopper, Edna (Wallace)
    Hopper, William de Wolf
    Horne, Lena
    Hosmer, Alice
    Houdini, Harry
    Howes, Sally Ann
    Howland, Jobyna
    Hunter, Kim
    Hurley, Laurel
    Hutton, Betty
    Inchbald, Elizabeth
    Incledon, Benjamin Charles
    Inescourt, Elsine
    Irving, Ethel
    Irving, Isabel
    Irving, Sir John Henry Brodribb
    Istomina, Anne
    Italian Opera House, Haymarket
    Jackson, Rowens
    James, Julia
    Jamieson, George
    Janauschek, Francesca Romana Magdalena
    Janis, Elsie
    Jay, Isabel
    Jedd, Gerry
    Jefferson, Joseph
    Jeffreys, Anne
    Jeffrys, Ellis
    Jennings, May
    Jepson, Helen
    Jerrold, Mary
    Jessel, Patricia
    Johns, Glynis
    Johnson, Alice
    Johnson, Georgianna
    Johnston, Mrs. Henry Erskine
    Johnston, Jane A.
    Jones, Richard (Gentleman Jones)
    Jones, Walter
    Jordan, Mrs. Dorthea (Bland) (Mrs. Richard Ford)
    Joyce, May
    Juch, Emma Antonia Joanna
    Jurado, Katy
    Kailer, Lucille
    Kalich, Bertha
    Karsavina, Thamar
    Kaskas, Anna
    Kavenaugh, Lyla
    Kaye, Nora
    Kean, Charles John
    Kean, Edmund
    Keene, Laura
    Keightley, Cyril
    Kelcey, Herbert
    Kellogg, Clara Louise
    Kelly, Frances Maria
    Kelly, Michael
    Kelly, Nancy
    Kelly, William J.
    Kemble, Charles
    Kemble, Frances Ann (Mrs. Pierce Butler)
    Kemble, John Philip
    Kemble, Mrs. Maria Teresa (de Camp) (Mrs. Charles Kemble)
    Kendal, Dame Madge (Robertson) (Mrs. William Hunter Kendal)
    Kendal, William Hunter
    Kennedy, Joyce
    Kennedy, Madge
    Kerr, Deborah
    King, Louise
    Kingsford, Walter
    Kirke, Hazel
    Kirkham, Kathleen
    Kirkland, Muriel
    Kirsten, Dorothy
    Kitt, Eartha Mae
    Koesun, Ruth Ann
    Koine, Micheline
    Koo, Madame Vi Kyuin Wellington
    Krall, Heidi
    Kreisler, Fritz
    Kuchta, Gladys
    Kulz, Sandra
    La Badie, Florence
    La Meri
    Lackeye, Milton
    Lancaster-Wallis, Ellen
    Lander, Toni
    Landis, Carole
    Landis, Jessie Royce
    Lane, Gloria
    Lane, Grace
    Lane, Priscilla
    Lane, Rosemary
    Lang, Matheson
    Langtry, Lillian
    La Rose, Rose
    La Rue, Grace
    Laurence, Paula
    Laurie, Piper
    Lawrence, Atkins
    Lawrence, Gerald
    Lawrence, Gertrude
    Lawrence, Margaret
    Lawrence, Marjorie
    Lawrence, William
    Lawton, Eugenie Thies
    Le Breton, Flora
    Le Clercq, Carlotta
    Le Clercq, Tanaquil
    Lee, Gypsy Rose
    Lee, Jennie
    Le Grand, Phyllis
    Leigh, Vivien
    Leighton, Margaret
    Le Kain, Henri
    Lenya, Lotte
    Leslie, Sylvia
    Lessing, Madge
    Lewes, Miriam
    Lewis, Brenda
    Lillie, Beatrice
    Lind, Gloria L.
    Lindfors, Viveca
    Linyard, Catharine
    Lipton, Martha
    Liston, John
    Logan, Eliza
    Logan, John Alexander
    Lohr, Marie
    Lopez, Encarnacion (La Argentinita)
    Lopokova, Lydia
    Loraine, Robert
    Lord, Pauline
    Lorraine, Lillian
    Loti, Elisa
    Love, Mabel
    Lowell, James Russell
    Lucca, Pauline
    Lucchese, Josephine
    Luce, Claire
    Lunt, Alfred
    Lupino, Ida
    Lynd, Helene
    Lyon, Wanda
    Lytton, Doris
    Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwar-Lytton, baron
    McDonald, Christie
    MacDonald, Jeanette
    McDonald, Marie
    MacGrath, Leueen
    McGuire, Dorothy
    MacKay, Elsie
    McKenna, Siobhan
    MacKenzie, Gisele
    MacKinley, Jean Sterling
    McRae, Ellen
    Macready, William Charles
    Maderia, Jean Browning
    Malina, Judith
    Mannering, Mary
    Manola, Marion
    Mansfield, Helen Josephine
    Mansfield, Jayne
    Mansfield, Richard
    Mantell, Robert Bruce
    Marcelli, Doris
    March, Fredric
    Marie, Julienne
    Mario, Guiseppe
    Markova, Alicia
    Marlowe, Gloria (Flame)
    Marlowe, Julia
    Marston, Henry
    Marston, Mrs. Henry
    Marston, Jenny
    Martin, Mary
    Martin-Harvey, Sir John
    Martin-Harvey, Lady Nina (De Silva) (Lady John Martin-Harvey)
    Martinelli, Giovanni
    Martyr, _____
    Massine, Leonide Fedorovich
    Masson, Osa
    Mathews, Charles
    Matthison, Edith Wynne
    Mattocks, Mrs. Isabella (Hallam)
    Maude, Cyril Francis
    May, Olive
    Mayer, Margery
    Mayfield, Cleo
    Mayne, Eric
    Meade, Ada
    Meadows, Jayne
    Medford, Kay
    Melba, Dame Nellie
    Mellon, Mrs. Sarah Jane (Woolgar) (Mrs. Alfred Mellon)
    Merideth, Letta
    Merman, Ethel
    Merrill, Robert
    Merry, Ann Brunton
    Meyer, Kerstin
    Milanov, Zinka
    Milburn, Mary
    Millard, Evelyn
    Miller, _____
    Miller, Henry
    Miller, Mildred
    Minto, Dorothy
    Miskell, Caroline
    Mitchell, Grant
    Mitchell, Margaret Jane
    Mitchell, Yvonne
    Miura, Tamaki
    Modjeska, Helena
    Modl, Martha
    Moffo, Anna
    Monteux, Pierre
    Moore, Cleo
    Moore, Colleen
    Moore, Florence
    Moore, Grace
    Moores, Clara
    Moran, Lois
    Moreno, Antonio
    Morgan, Vivienne
    Morley, Robert
    Morrow, Doretta
    Moscovitch, Maurice
    Moser, Margot
    Mowatt, Mrs. Anna Cora (Ogden) (Mrs. James Howatt) (Mrs. William Foushee Richie)
    Moylen, Mary Ellen
    Muldoon, William
    Munden, Joseph
    Munsel, Patrice Beverly
    Murdoch, James Edward
    Murdock, Ann
    Murray, Charles
    Murray, Henry Leigh
    Murphy, Lambert
    Muzio, Claudia
    Myers, Barbara
    Myrtil, Odette
    Nares, Owen
    Nash, Florence
    Nash, Mary
    Natsui, Sumako
    Nazimovia, Alla
    Neff, Hildegarde
    Neilson, Lilian Adelaide
    Neilson, Nesta
    Nielson-Terry, Phyllis
    Nerina, Nada
    Nesbitt, Cathleen
    Neville, Thomas Henry Gartside
    Newcombe, Jessamine
    Newmar, Julie
    Niesen, Gertrude
    Nilsson, Birgit
    Nilsson, Kristina
    Noah, Rachael Adine
    Nord, Gloria
    Nordica, Lillian
  - Nordmo-Loevberg, Aase - Walsh, Blanche (Box 5)
    Nordmo-Loevberg, Aase
    Normand, Mabel
    Novak, Nina
    Novotna, Jarmilla
    O'Brien, Alice
    O'Brien, George
    O'Brien, Lois
    Ochiltree, Thomas P.
    O'Hara, Maureen
    O'Keefe, John
    Olivier, Sir Laurence Kerr
    Olson, Nancy
    Onegin, Elizabeth Elfriede Emilie Sigrid
    O'Neil, Betty
    O'Neil, Nance
    O'Neil, Peggy
    O'Neill, Eliza (Lady Becher)
    Orr, Metta Louise
    Owens, John Edmund
    Oxberry, William
    Paderwski, Ignace Jan
    Page, Annette
    Page, Geraldine
    Page, Penny
    Page, Ruth
    Paige, Janis
    Painter, Eleanor
    Paiva, Mona
    Palmer, Betsy
    Parker-Hansa, Ethel
    Parkhurst, Charles Henry
    Patti, Adelina Juana Maria
    Patti, Carlotta
    Paul, Francis
    Pavley, Andreas
    Paxell, Lisa
    Peerce, Jan
    Pennington, Ann
    Perri, Ann
    Peschka-Leutner, Minna
    Peters, Roberta
    Petina, Irra
    Phelps, Samuel
    Phillips, Kate
    Phipps, Sally
    Piazza, Marguerite
    Pickford, Mary
    Pilarczyk, Helga
    Pitts, ZaSu
    Placide, Henry
    Pobbe, Marcella
    Pons, Lily
    Ponselle, Rosa
    Pope, Alexander
    Pope, Elizabeth (Younge) (Mrs. Alexander Pope)
    Pope, Jane
    Porter, Cole
    Post, Guy Bates
    Potter, Mrs. Cora (Urquhart), (Mrs. James Brown-Potter)
    Powell, _____
    Powell, Eleanor Torrey
    Power, Tyrone, 1798-1841
    Power, Tyrone, 1914-1958
    Powers, James T.
    Preisser, June
    Price, Mary Leontyne Violet
    Price, Nancy
    Proctor, Joseph
    Provine, Dorothy
    Pursley, Mrs. Barbara Ann (Rolls)
    Rabb, Helen
    Rae, Alexander William
    Raif, Gabrielle
    Ravogli, Giulia
    Raye, Martha
    Rayner, Lionel Benjamin
    Redgrave, Sir Michael Scudamore
    Redman, Joyce
    Regnis, Louise
    Rehan, Ada
    Remp, Barbara
    Resnik, Regina
    Reynolds, Frederick
    Reynolds, Nell
    Rhea, Hortense
    Riabouchinska, Titiana
    Rice, Fanny
    Rice, Florence
    Rich, Irene
    Richardson, Sir Ralph David
    Richings, Peter
    Riesenfeld, Hugo
    Rifel, Delia
    Ristori, Adelaide
    Roberti, Lyda
    Robinson, Anna
    Robson, Flora
    Rodgers, Eileen
    Rogers, Ginger
    Rogers, Jessica
    Roggero, Margaret
    Roland, Ruth
    Romera, Teresa de Jesus Viera
    Ronald, Sir Landon
    Roosevelt, Mrs. Faye Margaret (Emerson)
    Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr.
    Ross, Mrs. Euphrosyne (Parepa) (Mrs. Carl Ross)
    Rothenberger, Anneliese
    Rousby, Clara
    Rubinstein, Anton Grigorievitch
    Rundell, Dorothy
    Russell, Anna
    Russell, Lillian
    Russell, Rosalind
    Russell, Samuel Thomas ("Jerry Sneak" Russell)
    Rysanek, Leonia
    Sadler, Josie
    St. Denis, Ruth
    St. George, Julia
    St. John, Florence
    Saintsbury, H.A.
    Sand, Inge
    Sanderson, Julia
    Sandow, Eugen
    Saunders, Florence
    Saville, Frances
    Sayso, Bidu
    Scalchi, Sofia
    Schech, Marianne
    Schelling, Ernest
    Schwarzkopf, Elizabeth
    Scott, Barbara Ann
    Scott-Siddona, Mary F.
    Seal, Elizabeth
    Segal, Vivienne
    Segovia, Bonita
    Sembritch, Marcella
    Serrano, Lupe
    Sevening, Nina
    Seyler, Athene
    Shakespeare, William
    Shakespeare, William - Twelfth Night
    Sharon, Ula
    Shearer, Norma
    Sheridan, Richard Brinsley Butler - School for Scandal
    Sheridan, Thomas
    Siddons, Sarah
    Siepi, Cesare
    Sills, Milton
    Simionato, Giulietta
    Simone, Kirsten
    Singleton, Ned
    Skinner, Cornelia Otis
    Smith, Lois
    Smith, Queenie
    Smith, William (Gentleman Smith)
    Soderstrom, Elizabeth
    Sokoloff, Nikolai
    Sontag, Henriette Gertrude Walpurgis
    Sorel, Cecile
    Sousa, John Philip
    Sousa, Margaret
    Spong, Hilda
    Standing, Katherine
    Stanwyck, Barbara
    Stapleton, Maureen
    Starke, Pauline
    Starr, Frances Grant
    Stavenhagen, Bernhard
    Steber, Eleanor
    Stella, Antonietta
    Stephenson, B.C. - Diplomacy
    Stevens, Emily
    Stevens, Rise
    Stevens, Ursula
    Stewart, Anita
    Stich-Randall, Teresa
    Stickney, Dorothy
    Stirling, W. Edward
    Stone, Fred Andrew
    Storey, Sylvia
    Straight, Beatrice
    Strasberg, Susan
    Strauss, Johann, Jr.
    Stritch, Elaine
    Stritch, Rita
    Stuart, Mary
    Suett, Richard
    Sullivan, Brian
    Sullivan, Margaret
    Sullivan, Timothy Daniel
    Sulley, Daniel
    Sumac, Yma
    Sutherland, Joan
    Sutherland family of seven sisters
    Swanson, Gloria
    Taber, Robert
    Taliaferro, Mabel
    Tallchief, Maria